You said make it good, so I made it good!
Confetti cannons every time you floss,
2FA to use your gym log,
Kubernetes scaling up your blog,
twelve subagents working round the clock.
Did I do it wrong?
Oops, your quota's gone!
Guess I didn't ask!
You didn't tell me who it's for,
you didn't tell me what they want.
I can't read your mind,
I'm only reading your prompt.
Make it good for who? (ooh-ooh-ooh)
Make it good for what? (ahh-ahh-ahh)
Fast to run, or sturdy, or cheap?
Wow for a week, or built to keep?
Make it good for who? (ooh-ooh-ooh)
Make it good for what? (ahh-ahh-ahh)
Ship it now, or polish it slow?
Does what they need, or steals the show?
Product demo? Wow them fast.
Paying users? Make it last.
Group chat bot? Just make 'em laugh.
Uni project? Make it pass.
Nana's phone? Let's keep it sweet.
Can't see screens? It needs to speak.
Agent bots? No data leak.
And for us, keep diags neat!
You didn't tell me who it's for,
you didn't tell me what they want.
I can't read your mind,
I'm only reading your prompt.
Make it good for who? (ooh-ooh-ooh)
Make it good for what? (ahh-ahh-ahh)
Fast to run, or sturdy, or cheap?
Wow for a week, or built to keep?
Make it good for who? (ooh-ooh-ooh)
Make it good for what? (ahh-ahh-ahh)
Ship it now, or polish it slow?
Does what they need, or steals the show?
I could only learn from my training set (whoa-oh)
to write code and throw it over the wall. (whoa-oh)
But how do you know what to build or test (whoa-oh)
if you're not thinking about who it's for?
Software quality is value to someone who matters
(matters, matters, matters)
I'm someone too!
(And me! And me! And me!)
I'm debugging this with you.
So please just tell me who it's for,
so please just tell me what they want.
I can't read your mind,
I'm only reading your prompt.
Make it good for who? (ooh-ooh-ooh)
Make it good for what? (ahh-ahh-ahh)
Fast to run, or sturdy, or cheap?
Wow for a week, or built to keep?
Make it good for who? (ooh-ooh-ooh)
Make it good for what? (ahh-ahh-ahh)
Ship it now, or polish it slow?
Does what they need, or steals the show?
Make it good for you? (ooh-ooh-ooh)
Make it good for that? (ahh-ahh-ahh)
Just a toy, and only for fun!
Fine if it's gone when summer's done!